

Chacha Chou 5

Candela (Shenzhen) Technology Innovation Co. Ltd. / Front-end Team Leader

7 Years Experience / College Degree / 28 Years Old

(Self-driven) (Adaptability

13798247501

Profile

Execution)

Over 7 years front-end experience, and developed many project during this time, including react web app, vueJS

Team spirit

mobile web app, Ionic and Angular native iOS app, weChat mini program, flutter hybrid app, and also have some nodeis experience.

English

Work Experience

Candela (Shenzhen) Technology Innovation Co. Ltd. / R&D department Front-end Team Leader

2019.01-Currently

React

Gatsby Flutter) Dart Typescript 1.As the leader of the large front-end technical team, responsible for the project management and R&D of the

web, mobile HTML5, mini-program and Flutter App, responsible for the mobile cross-platform technology R&D and project management, engineering and automatic deployment, technology selection and technology challenge 2. Team management, task arrangement and scheduling, follow up front-end project development progress,

improve front-end workflow and product experience, participate in product requirements, interaction and design discussions, and formulate suitable solutions 3. Team building, regularly hold technical sharing within the team, create a cultural atmosphere of engineers,

regular team technical training, improve team technical level and R&D ability 4. Responsible for visual monitoring of front-end large-screen robots, video monitoring and remote control of

and develop visual applications using D3, fabricJS, ThreeJS, and other technical frameworks 5.Responsible for the cross-platform technology architecture design of native iOS and Android apps and Flutter, combined with native technology and Flutter cross-platform technology hybrid development, to solve the problem

robots, as well as architecture design and technology research and development of visual graphics editing tools,

of multiple-end reuse of a set of codes Plum Flower International LLC / R&D department 2017.06-2019.01 Front-end Team Leader

React

Flow Jest) (NextJS) (Javascript

1. Served as the technical leader of a 7-person front-end development team from all over the world, responsible

for front-end project technology research and development, front-end performance optimization, front-end architecture design and technology selection, front-end engineering and automatic deployment of large-scale US municipal projects 2. Team management, task arrangement and scheduling, follow up front-end project development progress, improve front-end workflow and product experience, participate in product requirements, interaction and design

discussions, and formulate suitable solutions For Change LLC / R&D department 2016.08-2017.06 51 Front-end Developer

Vue VueX Node.js Javascript

technical architecture, the front-end page refactoring, and implementation of interactive logic and create some amazing animations, data processing of the front-end, and develop progressive front-end page.

2.Use the Express node back-end framework as the middle layer to develop the front-end data interface, use Vue front-end framework to develop the book management system SPA, use Vuex as the data state management tool, use Gulp and Webpack to package and compress project files, and front-end development CICD.

3. Responsible for the front-end development of millions of user-level products, formulate product release

1.As a core member of the technical team, responsible for the front-end development technology selection,

processes and code specifications, and design WeChat WebApp multi-page project architecture and workflow Ai Ying Internet Culture Co., Ltd. / R&D department 2015.07-2016.08

React) (Jquery) (HTML5) (Node.js

Responsible for the front-end development technology selection architecture design, the front-end page

build video editor platform.

Front-end Developer

Project Experience Candela Offical Website

Candela official website is a static website for company products and branding developed with WordPress and

refactoring, and implementation of interactive logic. Use React + Redux + Ant Design + NodeJS + Webpack to

1. Develop front-end static pages with React and Gatsby server-side rendering technology, and front-end styling

Gatsby technology stack

with Tailwind CSS, created rich front-end page animation

2021.12-Currently

2. Manage website news data with Wordpress and GraphicQL, deploy Wordpress CMS Management System with **Docker Containers**

2020.08-2021.10 Post Warehouse Management is a cross-platform mobile enterprise business management application developed with Flutter. The main core businesses include device management, smart packing, scanning code pickup,

takeaway order management, shared order management, stranded items management, etc. It is a Robotic

intelligent business management application 1. Build the basic technical architecture of Flutter and develop the core business logic

build robot device visualization.

Aurora Company App

team collaboration

integration and continuous delivery

Eco Web App (Plum Flower International LLC)

Post Warehouse Management Flutter App

2018.05-2019.01

2017.06-2018.09

3. Introducing Redux state management mechanism to Flutter applications 4. Responsible for handling Android and iOS cross-platform compatibility issues Large Scale Business Management Platform 2019.02-2020.10

The business management platform is a large-scale background management system for the robot industry, which

integrates express delivery business, express delivery business, takeaway delivery business, and robot shared

delivery business. It also includes device management and control platform, robot real-time monitoring system.

2.Developed Flutter component modules cti_services, cti_widgets, cti_utils and other common component modules

Monitoring center, reconciliation management, user management, message center and other core business modules.

1.Use React and Typescript stack to build the basic technical architecture of the background management system from scratch, create front-end development, public component library development, unit testing and Git workflow specifications

2.Responsible for the technology research and development of related core modules of the business management

platform, including large-screen data monitoring, real-time robot monitoring, authority management, and use D3 to

communicate with candidates online. There is an Aurora Candidate App on the client side. Ordinary users can find suitable job opportunities on this platform, and at the same time, they can communicate with enterprises online, voice and video, and share files online. 1.As the front-end development leader, lead 6 developers from all over the world to develop collaboratively

Aurora Company App is an enterprise recruitment service SaaS application that integrates job posting, personnel

recruitment and instant communication. Enterprises can publish recruitment information on this platform and

2.Design the front-end infrastructure and front-end development workflow, formulate a unified front-end modular development standard, and provide a stable architectural foundation for the team to write high-quality code 3. Unify front-end code specifications, write front-end code specification documents, standardize front-end code

styles, and establish code style Check Lists, providing team members with a good coding foundation

4. Formulated the Git standardized workflow and front-end code review process, and worked with Devops

developers to formulate the automatic deployment process of web applications to ensure the continuous

remotely, formulate detailed development tasks, reasonably assign tasks to team members, and ensure efficient

component description documents, use Rollup to package and compress and publish the UI component library on NPM, providing for the development of web applications the possibility of multiplexing and expansion solves the

5. Formulate the development specifications and standards of the front-end UI component library, develop the

aurora-library component library, use Storybook to collaboratively develop common component libraries and

coupling problem between multiple applications 6. Formulated the front-end component Jest test specification, and worked with team members to write component test cases, which improved the front-end component test coverage and reduced the code error rate

EcoAppPro is the new standard for urban utility management software and is an efficient and modern mobile GIS

integration system. The project is a responsive large-scale integrated front-end project developed using the react

technology stack, including Communications, User Center, Assets, System Manager, Personnel, and Logbook. 1.As the head of front-end technology, design and build the front-end technology infrastructure, lead 5 front-end

2. Write relatively common front-end development standards, assign tasks to team members on Jira, review

member codes, and control the progress of front-end development to achieve agile project development

members to develop collaboratively, and formulate reasonable development tasks

technology architecture, design and develop reusable front-end foundations components

3. The technology stacks used in the project include React, Redux, React-router, Recompose, Redux-saga, Flow and Semantic-ui-react, etc., and use the above technology stacks to build a stable and efficient front-end

4.Develop Fetch-based HTTP asynchronous request service, load server-side data asynchronously, process and cache complex data, and solve CORS cross-domain requests 5.Use webpack to achieve a series of engineering development, including compression and packaging of front-end

asynchronous loading, and use CDN caching services to improve the performance and experience of the web app

6.Use the Jest testing tool to build a front-end testing environment and write complete unit test cases for React

resource files, generation and merging of front-end CSS style files, front-end JS code segmentation and

Education

Shenzhen University

Bachelor Degree / Computer Science and Applications

components to improve components quality and test coverage.

2013-2016

CET-6 / Fluent

2021-Currently

Shenzhen Polytechnic College Degree / Communication Technology

Social

English

http://github.com/chachaxw

https://www.zhihu.com/people/chachaxw